const FisData = [
    {
      question: "What is Financial Intermediary?",
      answer:
        "Moshav Microfinance Bank (MMBL) – an MCL subsidiary – plays a crucial role in provisioning accessible financial intermediary services to underserved populations. By offering a range of tailored financial products and services (e.g. Micro Credit, Savings & Deposit Accounts, Insurance Services, Payment & Remittance Services, Pension, Group Lending & Solidarity Groups, Financial Literacy & Education, Non-Collateral & Agricultural Financing, and Digital Financial Services) to low-income individuals, smallholder farmers, and MSMEs. To gain access to the financial resources required to improve their economic status, grow their businesses, and enhance their overall quality of life."
    },
    {
      question: "Is MCL’s Financial Intermediary Services Regulated?",
      answer:
        "MCL’s Financial Intermediary Services are regulated by the Central Bank of Nigeria under the Microfinance Policy, Regulatory and Supervisory Framework for Nigeria. Moshav Microfinance Bank Ltd, a subsidiary of MCL, shall be incorporated and supervised based on this framework. Also, as the Securities Exchange Commission’s licensee for Commodities Warehousing and Collateral Management, MCL is registered to provide collateral management services and certify and operate commodities warehouses."
    },
    
  ];


  const IaasData = [
    {
      question: "What is MCL’s Infrastructure-As-As-Service (IAAS)?",
      answer:
        "MCL’s Infrastructure-As-A-Service (IAAS) is a service model that provides agribusinesses access to essential infrastructure resources on a flexible, pay-per-use basis. This model allows local farmers and MSMEs participating in MCL programs to leverage advanced infrastructure (e.g. warehousing and cold storage, food processing plants, packaging units, logistics and distribution, Energy Solutions, Water Management, Equipment Leasing and Maintenance, etc.) without the need for significant upfront capital investment.",
        li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",
        li7: "",
        li8: "",
        li9: "",
        li10: ""
    },
    {
      question: "How Does MCL’s IAAS benefit agribusinesses?",
      answer:
        "MCL’s Infrastructure-As-A-Service (IAAS) offers agribusinesses a comprehensive and flexible solution to meet infrastructural needs by reducing capital expenditure, enhancing productivity, providing scalability and flexibility, improving quality and compliance, mitigating risks, enhancing market access, allowing our clients to focus on core activities, supporting innovation and sustainability, offering comprehensive support and maintenance, and providing financial solutions. MCL’s IAAS significantly boosts agribusinesses' efficiency, competitiveness, and sustainability.",
        li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",
        li7: "",
        li8: "",
        li9: "",
        li10: ""
    },
    {
      question: "How Can I Access MCL’s Infrastructure-As-A-Service?",
      answer:
        "Please kick-start the following step-by-step process:",
        li1: "Contact MCL via email or register on our website to express interest;",
        li2: "MCL will contact you to schedule a consultation to discuss your needs;",
        li3: "Conduct a needs assessment with MCL;",
        li4: "Receive a customized proposal;",
        li5: "Review, negotiate, and sign the service agreement;",
        li6: "Set up infrastructure and receive training;",
        li7: "Access ongoing support and management;",
        li8: "Monitor and optimize infrastructure;",
        li9: "Scale services as needed;",
        li10: "Renew the contract and plan long-term.",
    }
  ];

  const CommodityData = [
    {
      question: "What is a Commodities Warehouse?",
      answer:
        "A commodities warehouse is a specialized facility for storing, managing, and handling agricultural and other commodities. MCL’s warehouses will play a critical role in the supply chain by ensuring that commodities are stored in optimal conditions to preserve their quality and value until they are needed for processing or sale."
    }
  ];

  const ClusterData = [
    {
      question: "What are Commodities Brokerage Services in Agribusiness?",
      answer:
        "Commodities Brokerage Services in agribusiness refer to the professional services provided by brokers who facilitate the buying and selling agricultural commodities. These services connect producers, processors, traders, and investors within the agricultural supply chain. Through our platforms, MCL offers market access and connectivity for buyers and sellers. It facilitates price discovery and transparency, enabling participants to deploy flexible risk management instruments.",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: "",
        des9: "",
        des10: "",
        des11: "",
        des12: "",
        li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",

    },
    {
      question: "How Does MCL’s Commodities Brokerage Service Work?",
      answer:
        "MCL’s Commodities Brokerage Service operates as an intermediary between buyers and sellers of agricultural commodities, facilitating trades, managing risks, and providing essential market information.  Step-by-Step Process of MCL’s Commodities Brokerage Service:",
        li1: "Client Onboarding:",
        li2: "Market Analysis & Strategy Development:",
        li3: "Trade Execution:",
        li4: "Post-Trade Services:",
        li5: "Settlement and Delivery:",
        li6: "Ongoing Support and Reporting:",
        des1: "Needs Assessment: MCL begins by understanding the specific needs and objectives of the client, whether they are producers, traders, or investors.",
        des2: "Account Setup: The client’s account is set up, including necessary legal and regulatory compliance checks.",
        des3: "Initial Consultation: Our experts consult with the client to develop a trading strategy based on current market conditions and client goals.",
        des4: "Risk Management Planning: Strategies for hedging and risk mitigation are formulated and tailored to the client’s risk appetite and market exposure.",
        des5: "Order Placement: Clients place buy or sell orders through MCL’s brokerage platform. Orders can be placed for spot trades, futures, or options.",
        des6: "Matching and Execution: MCL matches orders with suitable counterparties and executes the trades on behalf of the client.",
        des7: "Confirmation and Documentation: Trade confirmations and relevant documents are provided to both parties, ensuring transparency and record-keeping.",
        des8: "Quality Control: MCL ensures that the quality and quantity of the commodities meet the agreed standards before finalizing the trade.",
        des9: "Payment Processing: MCL facilitates the financial settlement of the trade, ensuring timely payment processing.",
        des10: "Logistics Coordination: Coordinating logistics for the delivery of commodities, including transportation and storage arrangements.",
        des11: "Market Updates: Regular updates on market conditions and price movements are provided to clients.",
        des12: "Performance Reporting: Periodic reports on the performance of trades and overall market strategy are shared with clients."

    },
    {
      question: "What types of activities are included in Cluster Market Support?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres.",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: "",
        des9: "",
        des10: "",
        des11: "",
        des12: "",
        li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",
    }
  ];
  
  const HomeData = [
    {
      question: "What Services Does Moshav Capital Ltd (MCL) Provide to Agribusiness Enterprises?",
      answer:
        "As an economic empowerment platform, MCL offers a unique blend of accessible financial intermediaries, commodities warehousing, collateral management, cluster marketing support, commodities brokerage, and shared infrastructure-as-a-service solutions. These services, designed with your needs in mind, are a testament to our commitment to empowering smallholder farmers, cooperatives, and MSMEs in the agribusiness sector.",
        li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",
        li7: "",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: ""
    },
    {
      question: "How can Moshav Capital's Financial Solutions benefit my agribusiness?",
      answer:
        "MCL’s financial intermediation is a game-changer for smallholder farmers and MSMEs. It plays a critical role in supporting their economic development and resilience by providing them with:",
        li1: "Integrated access to credit and other bespoke financial products (e.g. seasonal loans and working capital);",
        li2: "Micro Insurance and Micro Leasing to help mitigate and diversify risks and costs that might endanger smallholders and MSMEs;",
        li3: "Continuous Training and Advisory Services ensure that smallholder farmers and MSMEs can maintain financial records, plan businesses, manage their businesses, and be “bankable”;",
        li4: "Access to Technology and Markets, which will facilitate lowering of their transaction costs through efficiency and economies of scale;",
        li5: "Inclusive Growth through unflinching support for Women and Marginalized Groups.",
        li6: "",
        li7: "",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: ""
    },
    {
      question: "What is Commodity Warehousing?",
      answer:
        "MCL’s Commodities Warehousing is a comprehensive process that involves the following key aspects:",
      li1: "Storage Facilities: Our warehouses offer secure, climate-controlled environments to store agricultural commodities such as tomatoes, peppers, grains, processed beef, fish and other perishables.",
      li2: "Quality Management: MCL’s warehouses grade and quality control to ensure that stored commodities meet market standards.",
      li3: "Inventory Management: We will provide systematic inventory management services, which include tracking quantities, managing stock rotations, and maintaining detailed records.",
      li4: "Certification and Receipts: MCL issues warehouse receipts, certifying the quantity and quality of the stored commodities. The receipts can be used for various financial transactions.",
      li5: "",
      li6: "",
        li7: "",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: ""
    },
    {
      question: "How Does MCL’s Commodities Warehousing Help Agribusinesses?",
      answer:"",
      li1: "Reduces Post-Harvest Losses",
      li2: "Improves Market Access and Timing",
      li3: "Facilitates Access to Credit",
      li4: "Supports Value Addition",
      li5: "Enhances Operational Efficiency",
      li6: "Ensures Quality and Standards Compliance",
      li7: "Promotes Transparency and Trust",
      des1: "Preservation of Quality: Our proper storage conditions, a key part of our services, help maintain the quality of agricultural produce, reducing spoilage and losses due to pests, moisture, and other factors. This ensures that your hard work and investment are protected.",
        des2: "Extended Shelf Life: Our controlled environments extend the shelf life of commodities, allowing farmers to store products until market conditions are favourable.",
        des3: "Price Stability: When farmers store their produce with us, they can avoid selling during a market glut when prices are low and wait for better market conditions, thereby getting better prices.",
        des4: "Market Linkages: MCL, with its strong connections with buyers, can facilitate sales, improving market access for farmers and agribusinesses. This opens up new possibilities and opportunities for your business, fostering a sense of optimism and hope.",
        des5: "Aggregation: For smallholder farmers, warehousing facilitates produce aggregation, making it easier to sell in bulk and negotiate better prices.",
        des6: "Collateral for Loans: MCL’s warehouse receipts can be used as collateral to obtain loans from Moshav Microfinance Bank and other partner banks. This access to credit can help farmers re-invest and expand their agribusinesses.",
        des7: "Trade Financing: As a licensed Securities Exchange Commission’s Commodities Warehousing and Collateral Management firm, MCL’s warehouse can enable trade financing, where agribusinesses can secure short-term finance to manage cash flows while their goods are stored.",
        des8: "Processing and Packaging: Our warehouses offer additional services like processing, cleaning, and packaging, which add value to the raw commodities and make them market-ready."
    },
    {
      question: "Is MCL’s Infrastructure-As-A-Service beneficial to agribusiness value chains?",
      answer:
        "Yes, MCL’s Infrastructure-As-A-Service model significantly benefits agribusiness value chains by reducing costs, enhancing productivity, improving market access, and promoting sustainability. By providing access to modern infrastructure and fostering collaboration, MCL helps agribusinesses become more competitive, resilient, and capable of scaling their operations. This support is especially crucial for smallholder farmers and MSMEs, who often face substantial barriers to accessing high-quality infrastructure independently.",
        li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",
        li7: "",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: ""
        
    },
    {
      question: "How Does MCL Support Cluster Marketing for Agribusinesses?",
      answer: "MCL's Cluster Marketing Support service relies on collective strategies that enable small- scale farmers and agribusinesses to overcome many of their challenges individually. By pooling resources, enhancing market access, providing financial and technical support, and advocating for favourable policies, MCL helps its members achieve better market outcomes, increased profitability, and sustainable growth.",
      li1: "",
        li2: "",
        li3: "",
        li4: "",
        li5: "",
        li6: "",
        li7: "",
        des1: "",
        des2: "",
        des3: "",
        des4: "",
        des5: "",
        des6: "",
        des7: "",
        des8: ""
    }
  ];


  const AboutData = [
    {
      icon: `<svg  width="50" height="50" viewBox="0 0 150 150" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_318_8308)">
      <path d="M56.25 87.5C56.25 97.8562 73.0375 106.25 93.75 106.25C114.462 106.25 131.25 97.8562 131.25 87.5C131.25 77.1438 114.462 68.75 93.75 68.75C73.0375 68.75 56.25 77.1438 56.25 87.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M56.25 87.5V112.5C56.25 122.85 73.0375 131.25 93.75 131.25C114.462 131.25 131.25 122.85 131.25 112.5V87.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M18.75 37.5C18.75 44.2 25.9 50.3875 37.5 53.7375C49.1 57.0875 63.4 57.0875 75 53.7375C86.6 50.3875 93.75 44.2 93.75 37.5C93.75 30.8 86.6 24.6125 75 21.2625C63.4 17.9125 49.1 17.9125 37.5 21.2625C25.9 24.6125 18.75 30.8 18.75 37.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M18.75 37.5V100C18.75 105.55 23.575 109.062 31.25 112.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M18.75 68.75C18.75 74.3 23.575 77.8125 31.25 81.25" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_318_8308">
      <rect width="150" height="150" fill="white"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>`,
      question: "Tailored Financial Solutions",
      listOne: "Access tailored credit facilities and financing options designed specifically for agribusinesses, addressing diverse needs and business goals.",
      listTwo: "Benefit from expert collateral management solutions to optimize asset utilization and secure financing for growth and expansion.",
      listThree: "Partner with leading insurance providers through Moshav Capital to obtain tailored micro insurance products covering crop, livestock, and equipment risks.",
      listfour: "Moshav Capital's services are uniquely crafted to address the specific challenges and goals of agribusinesses, providing personalized support for sustainable growth and success."
    },
    {
      icon: ` <svg width="50" height="50" viewBox="0 0 150 150" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_318_8319)">
      <path d="M25 87.5V68.75C25 55.4892 30.2678 42.7715 39.6447 33.3947C49.0215 24.0178 61.7392 18.75 75 18.75C88.2608 18.75 100.979 24.0178 110.355 33.3947C119.732 42.7715 125 55.4892 125 68.75V87.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M112.5 118.75C112.5 129.106 95.7125 137.5 75 137.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M25 87.5C25 84.1848 26.317 81.0054 28.6612 78.6612C31.0054 76.317 34.1848 75 37.5 75H43.75C47.0652 75 50.2446 76.317 52.5888 78.6612C54.933 81.0054 56.25 84.1848 56.25 87.5V106.25C56.25 109.565 54.933 112.745 52.5888 115.089C50.2446 117.433 47.0652 118.75 43.75 118.75H37.5C34.1848 118.75 31.0054 117.433 28.6612 115.089C26.317 112.745 25 109.565 25 106.25V87.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M93.75 87.5C93.75 84.1848 95.067 81.0054 97.4112 78.6612C99.7554 76.317 102.935 75 106.25 75H112.5C115.815 75 118.995 76.317 121.339 78.6612C123.683 81.0054 125 84.1848 125 87.5V106.25C125 109.565 123.683 112.745 121.339 115.089C118.995 117.433 115.815 118.75 112.5 118.75H106.25C102.935 118.75 99.7554 117.433 97.4112 115.089C95.067 112.745 93.75 109.565 93.75 106.25V87.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_318_8319">
      <rect width="150" height="150" fill="white"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>`,
      question: "Comprehensive support ecosystem",
      listOne: "Moshav Capital fosters collaborative marketing efforts among agribusinesses, facilitating partnerships and initiatives to access new markets and enhance visibility.",
      listTwo: "Access expert brokerage services through Moshav Capital to streamline trade and market access, ensuring efficient transactions and optimized distribution.",
      listThree: "Leverage Moshav Capital's IaaS solutions to optimize operations and reduce costs, benefiting from technology and infrastructure support tailored for agribusiness growth.",
      listfour: ""
    },
    {
      icon: `<svg width="40" height="40" viewBox="0 0 40 40" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_489_2330)">
      <path d="M10 15C10 17.6522 11.0536 20.1957 12.9289 22.0711C14.8043 23.9464 17.3478 25 20 25C22.6522 25 25.1957 23.9464 27.0711 22.0711C28.9464 20.1957 30 17.6522 30 15C30 12.3478 28.9464 9.8043 27.0711 7.92893C25.1957 6.05357 22.6522 5 20 5C17.3478 5 14.8043 6.05357 12.9289 7.92893C11.0536 9.8043 10 12.3478 10 15Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M20 25L25.6667 34.8167L28.33 29.4283L34.3267 29.815L28.66 20" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M11.3385 20L5.67188 29.8167L11.6685 29.4283L14.3319 34.815L19.9985 25" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_489_2330">
      <rect width="40" height="40" fill="white"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>
      `,
      question: "Reliable and Secure Warehousing",
      listOne: "Moshav Capital operates secure storage facilities licensed by regulatory authorities, ensuring optimal conditions for various commodities.",
      listTwo: "Clients receive official warehouse receipts from Moshav Capital, which can be used as collateral for financing, providing additional liquidity and flexibility for business operations.",
      listThree: "",
      listfour: ""
    },
    {
      icon: `<svg width="50" height="50" viewBox="0 0 150 151" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_318_8338)">
      <path d="M18.75 106.75L56.25 69.25L81.25 94.25L131.25 44.25" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M87.5 44.25H131.25V88" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_318_8338">
      <rect width="150" height="150" fill="white" transform="translate(0 0.5)"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>`,
      question: "Commitment to Innovation & Sustainability",
      listOne: "Moshav Capital is committed to delivering innovative solutions tailored for agribusinesses, ensuring long-term success through cutting-edge approaches and technologies.",
      listTwo: "We prioritize responsible resource management, promoting sustainable agricultural practices to minimize environmental impact and enhance long-term viability.",
      listThree: "Moshav Capital fosters knowledge sharing and collaborative partnerships within the agribusiness sector, creating synergies that drive sustainable growth and development.",
      listfour: ""
    },
  ]

  

const exportedData = {
    IaasData,
    ClusterData,
    FisData,
    CommodityData,
    HomeData,
    AboutData
}


export default exportedData;
  